http://www.aclj.org/privacy-policy

Search  |  Logout  |  Login  |  RegisterACLJ Profile CompletionVerified×Login CloseReset PasswordLogin×Register CloseRegisterReceive the latest news, updates, and contribution opportunities from ACLJ.× CloseToggle navigationNewsPetitionsVideosGet Legal HelpResourcesVictory ReportsOur MissionAbout ACLJAbout JayAbout JordanStaffLegal ResourcesGet our HelpLegal DocumentsFOIAGlobal Human Rights ReportsRadioListen to Radio ShowsFind a radio stationNewsPress ReleasesMedia MentionsNews Media RequestsGivingDonateLeave a LegacyDonateDONATEYour gift doubledListenBREAKING: President Trump and 18 States File at Supreme CourtListen NowBREAKING: President Trump and 18 States File at Supreme CourtNewsPetitionsVideosGet Legal HelpResourcesVictory ReportsOur MissionAbout ACLJAbout JayAbout JordanStaffLegal ResourcesGet our HelpLegal DocumentsFOIAGlobal Human Rights ReportsRadioListen to Radio ShowsFind a radio stationNewsPress ReleasesMedia MentionsNews Media RequestsGivingDonateLeave a LegacyDonateDONATEYour gift doubledPrivacy & Security PolicyBy accessing or using the ACLJ Web Site, you agree to the terms of the ACLJ Web Site Online Privacy Policy,
as outlined below. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site. The ACLJ Web
Site reserves the right to change the Online Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. Your
use of this site will be subject to the most current version of the Online Privacy Policy at the time of
such use.
Collection of Personal InformationWhen you engage in certain activities on this site, such as ordering information, signing petitions, making
donations, sending requests to the ACLJ, downloading forms, or requesting newsletter or email subscriptions
etc., the ACLJ Web Site may ask you to provide certain information about yourself by filling out and
submitting an online form. It is completely optional for you to engage in these activities. If you elect to
engage in these activities, however, the ACLJ Web Site may ask that you provide us personal information, such
as your first and last name, mailing address (including zip code), E-mail address, employer, job title and
department, telephone and facsimile numbers, and other personal identifying information. If you do not provide
the requested data with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.
How Your Personal Information is UsedThe ACLJ Web Site collects your information in order to record and support your participation in the
activities you select. For example, if you participate in petition drives or request assistance from the ACLJ,
your information is used to contact you and send appropriate materials.
Use of Personal InformationThe ACLJ Web Site recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of information collected on
this site. For this reason, the ACLJ reserves the option of contacting you at least one time about important
issues in which the ACLJ is involved. At that time, and with each subsequent email, the ACLJ will provide you
with the opportunity to "opt out" using our automated system. If you choose this option, you will receive no
further email from the ACLJ.
Protection of Your Personal InformationThe personal information that you provide in connection with making a donation to the ACLJ using the ACLJ
Web Site, classifies your data as Donor Registration Information. Donor Registration Information is protected
in several ways. First, it resides on a secure server that only selected ACLJ Web Site personnel and its
authorized users have access to via password. Second, the ACLJ Web Site encrypts your personal information
and thereby prevents unauthorized parties from viewing it. Personal information that you provide when
registering for a petition, or corresponding with the ACLJ, for example, also resides on a secure server
and is only accessible via password, however it is not encrypted.
Use of CookiesThe ACLJ Web Site currently uses cookies to reduce loading time.Updating Your Personal InformationYou have the right to access and correct your personal information at any time. With respect to Donor or
Registration Information, this may be accomplished by contacting us.You may also access and correct your personal information and privacy preferences by writing or calling
ACLJ Web Site at:The ACLJ Web Site
P.O.Box 90555
Washington, DC 20090-0555
(757) 226-2489
(757) 226-2836 (fax)
Privacy Related ComplaintsIf you believe that the ACLJ Web Site has not complied with this Online Privacy Policy with respect to your
personal information, you may write the ACLJ Web Site Privacy Officer at the address indicated above.
In your letter, please describe in as much detail as possible the ways in which you believe that the ACLJ has
not complied with the Official Web Site Online Privacy Policy. We will investigate your complaint promptly.
Please note that if you provide ACLJ Web Site with inconsistent privacy preferences (for example, by indicating
on one occasion that third parties may contact you with marketing offers and indicating on another occasion
that they may not), ACLJ Web Site cannot guarantee that your most recent privacy preference will be honored.
Also, please note that ACLJ Web Site is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-ACLJ Web
sites to which we may link.Connect with usReceive the latest news, updates, and contribution opportunities from ACLJ.SUBMITConnectwith Jay SekulowJaySekulow.comFacebookTwitteryoutubeRegentConnectwith Jordan SekulowJordanSekulow.comFacebookTwitterCareersWant to work for the ACLJ?ACLJ Careers PageConnectwith the ACLJFacebookTwitterYouTubeContact UsMEMBER SERVICES:1-800-342-2255PETITION LINE:1-877-989-2255JAY SEKULOW LIVE:1-800-684-3110lines open Mon-Fri noon to 1pm ESTMore Contact OptionsVisit our Global PartnersEuropean CentreSlavic CentreAfrican CentreBe Heard ProjectAmerican Center for Law and Justice | Washington D.C. | Copyright © 2020, ACLJ |
Privacy & Security Policy |
Annual ReportThe ACLJ is an organization dedicated to the defense of constitutional liberties secured by law.American Center for Law and Justice is a d/b/a for Christian Advocates Serving Evangelism,
Inc., a tax-exempt, not-for-profit, religious corporation as defined under Section 501(c)(3)
of the Internal Revenue Code, specifically dedicated to the ideal that religious freedom and
freedom of speech are inalienable, God-given rights. The Center's purpose is to engage legal,
legislative and cultural issues by implementing an effective strategy of advocacy, education
and litigation to ensure that those rights are protected under the law. The organization has
participated in numerous cases before the Supreme Court, Federal Court of Appeals, Federal
District Courts, and various state courts regarding freedom of religion and freedom of speech.
Your gift is very much appreciated and fully deductible as a charitable contribution. A copy
of our latest financial report may be obtained by writing to us at P.O. Box 90555, Washington,
DC 20090-0555.
